Agustin Camuzzi

Full Stack Web Developer

camuzziagustin@gmail.com || Phone: (+54) 266 4953687 || San Luis - San Luis, Argentina

Linkedin - Github - Portfolio

Full Stack Developer with a background in Web Design. Experienced in working with industry technologies (React.js, Redux, PostgreSQL, etc.) and possessing administrative knowledge gained from my work in a gastronomic company. Proficient in agile methodologies such as SCRUM. Solutions-oriented with strong teamwork, proactivity, communication, and leadership skills

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Node.js, Express, Vite, PostgreSQL. Libraries like SweetAlert2, Cloudinary. Proficient in agile methodologies like SCRUM and GitFlow and working with GitHub.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - 8 bits app

Aug. 2023 - Sep. 2023

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

- Designed and developed an app for game sales, including: Login, admin and user dashboards, shopping cart and payment, video game and user creation forms, and responsive design.
- Developed the front-end of the app with controlled forms, implemented Cloudinary and SweetAlert2 alerts, and designed the user profile. Assisted with problem-solving, debugging, and bug fixing as they arose.
- Link to repo: Front-End, Back-End
- Deployed app: 8-bits app

Full Stack Web Developer - Pokemon app

Jun. 2023 - Jul. 2023

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

- Designed and developed an app using a Pokemon API, including: landing page, home with filters and cards, search bar, detailed view of each Pokemon, controlled creation form, and about section
- Developed the app using React.js, Redux, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, Node.js, PostgreSQL.
- Link to repo: Repo

LANGUAGES

- English C1 Advanced. EF Standard English Test (EF SET). Credential
- Portuguese Advanced, fluent. 8 years of residency in São Paulo, Brazil.

PRIOR EXPERIENCE

Snap Food SRL

San Luis, Argentina

Administrative Position Nov. 2021 – Aug. 2023

- Managed company administration and delivery logistics.
- Daily stock management and control.
- Purchased supplies and coordinated payments and deliveries with suppliers.

Delivery Logistics Aug. 2021 - Nov. 2021

Organized and managed food deliveries with couriers in charge.

Courier Jun. 2021 – Aug. 2021

· Performed all food deliveries.

Travel Sales Representative

Tentación Turismo, San Luis, Argentina.

Sep. 2017 - Nov. 2019.

- Administrative tasks and customer service, selling travel packages (high school).
- Organized and led meetings, organized and participated (animated) in company events.
- Coordinated graduate trips to Punta del Este, Uruguay; Camboriu, Brazil; and Villa Carlos Paz, Cordoba.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical and practical training. 2022-2023.
- Third year of Electronic Engineering with OSD. UNSL. 2016-2019...

Current Academic Training

• Mobile App Development Course (Oct.2023 – Present). Google Activate

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Programming from Scratch Course. Egg Live. 2022.
- Mobile Application Development Course. Google Activate. 2023

OTHER INTERESTS

Volunteer at IEEE (Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers) at UNSL. Organized lectures, events, seminars, and workshops. Responsible for treasury and logistics. Participated in national meetings in Catamarca in 2017, Buenos Aires in 2018, and Bahía Blanca in 2019. Sep. 2016 – Nov. 2019..